Guide to the Giant Food Stores Advertising Collection, 1951-2001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Giant Food Stores Advertising collection 1951-2001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Giant Food Inc.
87.2 linear feet Extent: 17967 Items
Giant Foods, established in 1936, is one of the oldest enduring chains of supermarkets in the U.S., and primarily serves the Washington, D.C. area and surrounding states. The Giant Food Stores Advertising Collection spans the years 1951 through 2001 and includes bound, unbound, and microfilmed volumes of reductions of newspaper advertisements and circulars; oversize posters and banner advertisements; Supermarket News issues from the 1990s; advertising scrapbooks from the 1970s and 1980s; and a set of videotapes of broadcast commercials, that document daily local advertising for a major regional supermarket chain.
RL.00447
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Giant Food Stores Advertising Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift from the Naomi and Nehemiah Cohen Foundation, and the Jewish Historical Society of Greater Washington, in 2006 and 2010.
Historical Note
N.M. Cohen and Samuel Lehrman opened the first Giant store in Washington, D.C. in 1936. The store's operating philosophy sought to achieve a price advantage over competitors through a high-volume, self-service operation. As the company expanded, Giant integrated vertically through house-branded products and chain-owned meat packing plants. The company was an early adopter of many of the features now common among contemporary supermarkets, including: automated entrances; shopping carts; computerized inventory control and customer data; and checkout scanners. It was among the first grocery chains to include service centers, such as pharmacies, florists and bakeries, within their stores. Giant eventually expanded into Maryland, Delaware, and Virginia. The chain was purchased by the Dutch company Royal Ahold in 1998, but supermarkets and internet commerce still operate under the Giant name.
Collection Overview
The Giant Food Stores Advertising Collection spans the years 1951 through 2001 and includes bound, unbound, and microfilmed volumes of reductions of newspaper advertisements and circulars, along with a set of videotapes of broadcast commercials, that document daily local advertising for a major regional supermarket chain.
The collection is arranged by format into eight series: Adbank Commercials; Advertising File; Bound Advertisements; Food World Information Services (FWIS); Microfilm; Scrapbooks; Oversize Advertisements; and Printed Materials. The Adbank Commercials Series consists of videotaped commercials for Giant Foods, and some of its competitors, as compiled by the Adbank research firm. The Advertising File Series includes unbound reductions of Giant newspapers. The Bound Advertisements Series consists of bound volumes of reductions of newspaper advertisements and circulars, arranged by city. The Food World Information Services (FWIS) Series includes reductions of newspaper advertisements arranged by city, as compiled by FWIS. The Microfilm Series contains newspaper advertising archived on microfilm, arranged by city and newspaper title. The Scrapbook Series includes eight scrapbooks with fullpage newspaper advertisements, dating from 1970-1982. The Oversize Advertisements Series include posterboards and banners displayed in storefront windows. The Printed Materials Series includes an incomplete run of Supermarket News, a weekly trade magazine, dating from 1994-1998.
Subject Headings
Giant (Firm); Giant Food, Inc. (Washington, D.C.); Advertising -- Supermarkets; Advertising fliers; Advertising fliers -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Advertising -- Food -- United States; Advertising -- Food -- United States -- History; Circulars, Advertising; Grocery trade; Self-Service stores; Advertising -- Supermarkets; Microfilms; Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Contents of Collection
- Adbank Commercials Series, 1991-2000 (CLOSED), (5 boxes)
  Consists of 76 videotapes containing commercials from Adbank's Grocery, Drug, and Convenience Stores Category. Giant Foods as well as competitor commercials are represented. Arranged chronologically and numbered sequentially.
  Restrictions on Access: Original videotapes are closed to patron use. Reformatting for use copies is required before material can be viewed. A detailed listing of videotapes resides in the Collection Control File. Contact Research Services for current reformatting procedures and policies.
  - Originals (CLOSED)
    - Videotapes AV-O-1 through AV-O-16, 1991 Apr.-1993 Apr. (Box AV1)
    - Videotapes AV-O-17 through AV-O-33, 1993 May-1994 Aug. (Box AV2)
    - Videotapes AV-O-34 through AV-O-48, 1994 Sept.-1996 Jan. (Box AV3)
    - Videotapes AV-O-49 through AV-O-64, 1996 Feb.-1997 Aug. (Box AV4)
    - Videotapes AV-O-65 through AV-O-76, 1997 Sept.-2000 Jan. (Box AV5)
- Advertising File Series, 1965-1967, (3 boxes)
  Consists of unbound photocopy reductions of newspaper advertisements. Arranged chronologically.
  - 1965 Oct., (1-7 of 9 folders) (Box AF1)
  - 1965 Oct., (8-9 of 9 folders) (Box AF2)
  - 1965 Nov., (1-5 of 6 folders)
  - 1965 Nov., (6 of 6 folders) (Box AF3)
  - 1967 Nov., (6 folders)
- Bound Advertisements Series, 1951-1966, (24 boxes)
  Consists of reduced photocopies of newspaper advertisements and circulars, arranged alphabetically by city, and thereunder chronologically.
  - Annapolis
    - 1962 Sept.-1963 Dec. (Box BA1)
  - Baltimore
    - 1957 (Box BA1)
    - 1958-1961 (Box BA2)
    - 1962-1963 (Box BA3)
    - 1964-1966 June (Box BA4)
  - Baltimore-Richmond
    - 1956 (Box BA5)
  - Baltimore-Salisbury
    - 1959 (Box BA5)
  - Fredericksburg
    - 1963 May-Dec. (Box BA5)
    - 1964-1965 (Box BA6)
  - Glen Burnie
    - 1964 (Box BA6)
  - Newport News
    - 1958 (Box BA6)
    - 1960-1962 (Box BA7)
    - 1963-1965 (Box BA8)
  - Norfolk
    - 1957 (Box BA8)
    - 1958, 1960-1961 (Box BA9)
    - 1962-1964 (Box BA10)
  - Richmond
    - 1957 (Box BA10)
    - 1958, 1960-1961 (Box BA11)
    - 1962-1963, 1966 (Box BA12)
  - Richmond-Norfolk-Newport News
    - 1959 (Box BA13)
  - Salisbury
    - 1960-1961 (Box BA14)
    - 1962-1963 (Box BA15)
    - 1964-1966 June (Box BA16)
    - 1966 July-Dec. (Box BA17)
  - Washington, D.C.
    - 1951-1952 June (Box BA17)
    - 1952 July-1954 June (Box BA18)
    - 1954 July-1955 Dec. (Box BA19)
    - 1956, 1958 (Box BA20)
    - 1959-1960 (Box BA21)
    - 1961 (Box BA22)
    - 1962-1966 (Box BA23)
  - Multiple-City Circulars
    - 1961, 1964 (Box BA24)
- Food World Information Services (FWIS) Series, 1998-2001, (38 boxes)
  Consists of reduced photocopies of newspaper advertisements, compiled by the Food World Information Service. Arranged into Baltimore-Washington and Philadelphia area groups, and thereunder chronologically.
  - Baltimore-Washington
    - 1998 Apr.-June (Box FB1)
    - 1998 Aug.-Sept. (Box FB2)
    - 1998 Oct.-Nov. (Box FB3)
    - 1998 Dec. (Box FB4)
    - 1999 Jan.-Feb. (Box FB5)
    - 1999 Mar.-Apr. (Box FB6)
    - 1999 May-June (Box FB7)
    - 1999 July-Aug. (Box FB8)
    - 1999 Sept.-Oct. (Box FB9)
    - 1999 Nov.-Dec. (Box FB10)
    - 2000 Jan.-Feb. (Box FB11)
    - 2000 Mar.-Apr. (Box FB12)
    - 2000 May-June (Box FB13)
    - 2000 July-Aug. (Box FB14)
    - 2000 Sept.-Oct. (Box FB15)
    - 2000 Nov.-Dec. (Box FB16)
    - 2001 Jan-Feb. (Box FB17)
    - 2001 Mar-Apr. (Box FB18)
    - 2001 June-July (Box FB19)
    - 2001 Oct.-Nov. (Box FB20)
    - 2001 Dec. (Box FB21)
  - Philadelphia
    - 1999 June (Box FP1)
    - 1999 July-Aug. (Box FP2)
    - 1999 Sept. (Box FP3)
    - 1999 Sept.-Oct. (Box FP4)
    - 1999 Nov.-Dec. (Box FP5)
    - 2000 Jan.-Feb. (Box FP6)
    - 2000 Feb.-Apr. (Box FP7)
    - 2000 Apr.-June (Box FP8)
    - 2000 June-Aug. (Box FP9)
    - 2000 Aug.-Oct. (Box FP10)
    - 2000 Oct.-Nov. (Box FP11)
    - 2000 Nov.-2001 Jan. (Box FP12)
    - 2001 Jan.-Mar. (Box FP13)
    - 2001 Mar.-Apr., July (Box FP14)
    - 2001 July-Sept. (Box FP15)
    - 2001 Sept.-Nov. (Box FP16)
    - 2001 Dec. (Box FP17)
- Microfilm Series, 1967-1993, (393 reels)
  Consists of 393 reels of newspaper advertisements from a number of cities where Giant operated stores. Arranged into Advertisements, Circulars, and General Merchandise, then alphabetically by city and newspaper title, thereunder chronologically, and sequentially numbered.
  - Microfilm: Advertisements
    - Annapolis, Md.: Capital, 1988 July-Dec., 1989 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-001
    - Annapolis, Md.: Capital, 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-002
    - Annapolis, Md.: Evening Capital, 1970 May 4-July 29, MF-O-003
    - Annapolis, Md.: Evening Capital, 1987 Apr.-Dec., MF-O-004
    - Annapolis, Md.: Evening Capital, 1988 Jan.-June, MF-O-005
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1967 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-006
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1969 Jan.-Feb., MF-O-007
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1969 Mar.-May 4, MF-O-008
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1969 May 7-July 9, MF-O-009
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1969 July 13-Sept. 21, MF-O-010
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1979 Jan.-June, MF-O-011
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1980 Jan.-June, MF-O-012
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1980 July-Dec., MF-O-013
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1981 Jan.-June, MF-O-014
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1982 Apr.-Dec., MF-O-015
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1983 Jan.-Mar., MF-O-016
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1983 July-Sept., MF-O-017
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1983 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-018
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1984 Jan.-Sept., MF-O-019
    - Baltimore, Md.: News American, 1984 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-020
    - Charlottesville, Va.: Daily Progress, 1986 May-Dec., MF-O-021
    - Charlottesville, Va.: Daily Progress, 1987 Jan.-June, MF-O-022
    - Charlottesville, Va.: Daily Progress, 1987 July-Dec., MF-O-023
    - Charlottesville, Va.: Daily Progress, 1988 Jan.-June, MF-O-024
    - Charlottesville, Va.: Daily Progress, 1988 July-Dec., MF-O-025
    - Charlottesville, Va.: Daily Progress, 1989 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-026
    - Charlottesville, Va.: Daily Progress, 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-027
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1980 Jan.-June, MF-O-028
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1980 July-Dec., MF-O-029
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1981 Jan.-June, MF-O-030
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1981 July-1982 July, MF-O-031
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1982 Aug.-Dec., MF-O-032
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1983 Jan.-June, MF-O-033
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1983 July-Sept., MF-O-034
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1983 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-035
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1984 Jan.-Sept., MF-O-036
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1984 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-037
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1985 Jan.-Mar., MF-O-038
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1985 Apr.-June, MF-O-039
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1985 July-Sept., MF-O-040
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1985 Oct.-1986 Mar., MF-O-041
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1986 Apr.-1987 June, MF-O-042
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1987 July-Dec., MF-O-043
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1988 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-044
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1989 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-045
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick News, 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-046
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1980 Jan.-June, MF-O-047
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1980 July-Dec., MF-O-048
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1981 Jan.-June, MF-O-049
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1981 July-1982 July, MF-O-050
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1982 Aug.-Dec., MF-O-051
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1983 Jan.-June, MF-O-052
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1983 July-Sept., MF-O-053
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1983 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-054
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1984 Jan.-Sept., MF-O-055
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1984 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-056
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1985 Jan.-Mar., MF-O-057
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1985 Apr.-June, MF-O-058
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1985 July-Sept., MF-O-059
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1985 Oct.-1986 Mar., MF-O-060
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1986 Apr.-Dec., MF-O-061
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1987 Jan.-June, MF-O-062
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1987 July-Dec., MF-O-063
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1988 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-064
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1989 Jan.-June, MF-O-065
    - Frederick, Md.: Frederick Post, 1989 July-Dec., 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-066
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1967 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-067
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1967 Jan.-1970 Jan., MF-O-068
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1968 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-069
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1969 Mar. 3-May 5, MF-O-070
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1969 May 7-July 10, MF-O-071
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1969 July 14-Sept. 18, MF-O-072
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1969 Sept. 22-Nov. 24, MF-O-073
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1969 Dec. 1-1970 Jan. 29, MF-O-074
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1970 Feb. 4-Apr. 29, MF-O-075
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1970 May4-July 30, MF-O-076
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1980 Jan.-June, MF-O-077
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1980 July-Dec., MF-O-078
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1981 Jan.-June, MF-O-079
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1981 July-1982 Mar., MF-O-080
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1982 Apr.-Sept., MF-O-081
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1982 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-082
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1983 Jan.-June, MF-O-083
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1983 July-Sept., MF-O-084
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1983 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-085
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1984 Jan.-Sept., MF-O-086
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1984 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-087
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1985 Apr.-June, MF-O-088
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1985 July-Sept., MF-O-089
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1985 Oct.-1986 Dec., MF-O-090
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1987 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-091
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1988 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-092
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1989 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-093
    - Fredericksburg, Va.: Free Lance-Star, 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-094
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1969 Mar. 6-May 1, MF-O-095
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1969 Mar. 6-1970 Jan. 29, MF-O-096
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1969 May 8-July 10, MF-O-097
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1969 July 17-Sept. 11, MF-O-098
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1969 Sept. 25-Nov. 24, MF-O-099
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1969 Dec. 4-1970 Jan. 29, MF-O-100
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1987 Apr.-Dec., MF-O-101
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1988 Jan.-June, MF-O-102
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1988 July-Dec., 1989 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-103
    - Glen Burnie, Md.: Maryland Gazette, 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-104
    - Leesburg, Va.: Loudon Times (Mirror), 1969 Mar. 6-1970 Jan. 29, MF-O-105
    - Leesburg, Va.: Loudon Times (Mirror), 1970 May 7-July 30, MF-O-106
    - Manassas, Va.: Journal Messenger, 1988 Mar.-Dec., MF-O-107
    - Manassas, Va.: Journal Messenger, 1989 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-108
    - Manassas, Va.: Journal Messenger, 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-109
    - Richmond, Va.: News Leader, Times Dispatch, 1968 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-110
    - Richmond, Va.: News Leader, Times Dispatch, 1969 Jan.-Feb., MF-O-111
    - Richmond, Va.: News Leader, Times Dispatch, 1969 Mar.-May 1, MF-O-112
    - Richmond, Va.: News Leader, Times Dispatch, 1969 July 14-Sept. 18, MF-O-113
    - Richmond, Va.: News Leader, Times Dispatch, 1969 Dec. 1-1970 Jan. 29, MF-O-114
    - Rockville, Md.: Montgomery County Sentinel, 1969 Mar. 5-May 1, MF-O-115
    - Rockville, Md.: Montgomery County Sentinel, 1969 July 10, MF-O-116
    - Rockville, Md.: Montgomery County Sentinel, 1969 July 17-Sept. 11, MF-O-117
    - Rockville, Md.: Montgomery County Sentinel, 1969 Sept. 25-Nov. 20, MF-O-118
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1968 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-119
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1969 Jan.-Feb., MF-O-120
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1969 Mar.-May 1, MF-O-121
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1969 May 4-July 10, MF-O-122
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1969 Sept. 24-Nov. 30, MF-O-123
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1969 Dec. 3-1970 Jan. 28, MF-O-124
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1970 Feb. 1-Apr. 29, MF-O-125
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1970 May-July, MF-O-126
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1980 Jan.-June, MF-O-127
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1980 July-Dec., MF-O-128
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1981 Jan.-June, MF-O-129
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1981 July-Dec., MF-O-130
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1982 Apr.-Dec., MF-O-131
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1983 Jan.-June, MF-O-132
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1983 July-Sept., MF-O-133
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1983 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-134
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1984 Jan.-Sept., MF-O-135
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1984 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-136
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1985 Apr.-June, MF-O-137
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1985 July-Sept., MF-O-138
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1985 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-139
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1987 Jan.-June, MF-O-140
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1987 July-Dec., MF-O-141
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1988 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-142
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1989 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-143
    - Salisbury, Md.: (Daily) Times, 1990 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-144
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1967 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-145
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1968 Jan.-1970 Jan., MF-O-146
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1970 Feb.-May 1, MF-O-147
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1970 May 4-July 30, MF-O-148
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1970 Aug.-Oct. 1, MF-O-149
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1970 Oct. 5-Dec., MF-O-150
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1971 Jan.-Feb., MF-O-151
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1971 Mar.-Apr., MF-O-152
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1971 May-July 1, MF-O-153
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1971 July 6-Sept., MF-O-154
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1971 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-155
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1972 Jan.-Mar. 4, MF-O-156
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1972 Mar. 6-Apr., MF-O-157
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1972 May-July 27, MF-O-158
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1972 July 30-Sept., MF-O-159
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1972 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-160
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1973 Jan.-Mar., MF-O-161
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1973 Apr.-June, MF-O-162
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1973 July-Sept., MF-O-163
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1973 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-164
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1974 Jan.-Mar., MF-O-165
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1974 Apr.-June, MF-O-166
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1974 July-Sept., MF-O-167
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1974 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-168
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1975 Jan.-Mar., MF-O-169
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1975 Apr.-June, MF-O-170
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1975 July-Sept., MF-O-171
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1975 Oct.-Dec., MF-O-172
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1976 Jan.-Mar., MF-O-173
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1976 Apr.-July, MF-O-174
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1976 Aug.-Sept., MF-O-175
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1976 Oct.-Nov., MF-O-176
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1976 Dec.-1977 Jan., MF-O-177
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Feb.-Mar., MF-O-178
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Apr.-May, MF-O-179
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 June-July, MF-O-180
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Aug.-Sept., MF-O-181
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Oct.-Nov., MF-O-182
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1977 Dec., MF-O-183
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 Jan.-Apr., MF-O-184
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 May-July, MF-O-185
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 Aug.-Nov., MF-O-186
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1978 Dec.-1979 Feb., MF-O-187
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Giant advertising, 1979 Mar.-May, MF-O-188
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1967 Jan.-June, MF-O-189
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1967 July-Dec., MF-O-190
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1968 Jan.-Dec., MF-O-191
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Jan.-Feb., MF-O-192
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Mar.-May 8, MF-O-193
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 May 8-July 11, MF-O-194
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 July 14-Sept. 22, MF-O-195
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Sept. 24-Dec. 1, MF-O-196
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1969 Dec. 4-1970 Jan. 30, MF-O-197
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 Feb. 2-May 1, MF-O-198
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 May 4-July, MF-O-199
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 Aug.-Oct. 1, MF-O-200
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1970 Oct. 5-Dec., MF-O-201
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 Jan.-Feb., MF-O-202
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 Mar.-Apr., MF-O-203
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 May-July 1, MF-O-204
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 July 6-Oct. 1, MF-O-205
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1971 Oct. 4-Dec., MF-O-206
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 Jan.-Mar. 2, MF-O-207
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 Mar. 6-Apr., MF-O-208
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 May-July 28, MF-O-209
    - Washington, D.C.: Post--Competition advertising, 1972 July 30-Sept., MF-O-210